unf.edu 2012-06-13

# University of North Florida - Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting the University of North Florida Website. Your privacy is very important to us. Simply stated, we do not collect personal information about you when you visit our Website unless you choose to make such information available to us.

When you visit our Website, our Web server automatically recognizes only the Internet domain and IP address from which you accessed our website. This information does not result in the identification of your personal e-mail address or other personal information.

In addition, we gather information regarding the volume and timing of access to our Website by collecting information on the date, time and Webpages accessed by visitors to the Website. We do this so that we can improve the content of our Website, and this information is not shared with other organizations. Only aggregate information is collected and individual visitors' personal information is not identified.

If you choose to share personal information with us - by sending us a message or filling out a form with personal information - we will use the information only for the purposes you authorized. Some of the information may be saved for a designated period of time to comply with Florida's archiving policies, but we will not disclose the information to third parties or other government agencies, unless required to do so by law. ****

**Under Florida law, many e-mails to UNF are public record.**  If you do not want your e-mail address released in response to a public records request, do not send electronic mail to the University.  Instead, contact the office you wish to contact by phone or in writing.   

If you have other questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to e-mail us at [webmaster@unf.edu](mailto:webmaster@unf.edu?subject=Internet%20Privacy%20Policy "webmaster").
